FLAVIEN CHAMAY

Hi, I'm a junior IT Python developer searching for new opportunities in France and beyond. I'm a Tech and Math enthusiast with a passion for A.I. and Backend development. I lived in Canada and in Europe, I have therefore experienced two different work worlds and have a certain flexibility towards that.



CONTACT

flavien.chamay@protonmail.com

**** +33 06 80 44 71 60

Toulouse, France

My Website (under construction)

github.com/flavienChamay

in linkedin.com/in/flavienchamay/

IT SKILLS

Programming Languages

Python

C

Java **OCaml**

SQL

LaTeX

Operating Systems

Linux Manjaro | Ubuntu

Windows 10 | 7

Software & Tools

GitHub/Git

Emacs

PyCharm

Eclipse

Heroku/Linode



Django

Blockchain

A.I.

Languages

English C2 grade **Native French**



CERTIFICATES & RECOMMENDATIONS

HackerRank Python Basic HackerRank Problem Solving Basic EFSET Standard English Test C2 Recommendation Letter from B&D

INTERESTS

A.I., Extraterrestrial life, Mathematical logic, Hacking.

PROJECTS

- Web Blog (Django, Heroku, Personal project in progress).
- Simple Blockchain (Python, Personal project in progress): coding of the proof of work, the wallet and data encryption.
- Tic-Tac-Toe Game (Python, Personal project in progress): Minimax algorithm for computer player, CLI interface, save/load mechanisms.
- Planning by satisfiability of logical formulas (Touist, Academic project): coding, modeling and benchmarking of logic problem solving A.I..
- NeoCampus, real-time sensors (Java, Academic project): GUI coding and data re-
- Caesar encryption (C, Academic project): encryption/decryption of text files.
- Websites (Google site): Creation and maintenance for various clients.

WORK HISTORY

2017 - 2020

Auterive & Toulouse, France

Tutor for private lessons in Maths and C.S.

🛗 April 2011 - August 2011

Staples

Quebec, Canada

Computer Repairman & **IT Consultant**

February 2008 - June 2010 Becton, Dickinson and Company Quebec, Canada

Packaging Operator

EDUCATION

2017 - 2020

Paul Sabatier University Toulouse, France

2011 - 2016

Paul Sabatier University Toulouse, France

iii 2010

CEGEP François-Xavier-Garneau Quebec, Canada

C.S. Bachelor Degree

1st & 2nd cycle in Physics 2nd cycle in Maths

High School Diploma in S.T.E.M.

GENERAL SKILLS

Model/specify/integrate/maintain/develop an app Assess client's need Analyse origin of malfunction Optimize algo in time/space complexity Identify/protect confidential data Understand/write doc. in Eng/Fr

HOBBIES & OCCUPATIONS

